<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Test_links</title>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 14:03:23 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>
      Cardano: Ledger Starts Letting $ADA Investors Buy, Send and Receive Directly on Ledger Live
      </title>
      <description>
      <p>French <a href="https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2022/06/cardano-ledger-starts-letting-ada-investors-buy-send-and-receive-directly-on-ledger-live/">cryptocurrency</a> hardware wallet manufacturer Ledger has finally added support for Cardano ($ADA) and is now letting users buy, send, 
      and receive their tokens directly on Ledger Live, the application for managing cryptoassets on their devices.</p><p>Paris-headquartered Ledger 
      was co-founded in 2014 by Eric Larchevêque, Nicolas Bacca, Joel Pobeda, and Thomas France. It first announced it was moving to support ADA back
      in April of this year.</p><p>In an announcement, Ledger wrote that Cardano-related features are currently available on Ledger Live’s desktop version
      while mobile support is “coming soon.” The firm noted that with the ADA integration, Ledger Live now supports all top 10 cryptocurrencies by 
      market capitalization.</p><p>To <a href="https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2022/06/cardano-ledger-starts-letting-ada-investors-buy-send-and-receive-directly-on-ledger-live/">manager</a> 
      their $ADA via <a href="https://it.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSDT/?exchange=BINANCE">Ledger’s devices</a>, users must create an ADA account, but don’t need to create an additional 
      wallet. They can also buy the cryptocurrency directly through the applications. The French cryptocurrency hardware wallet manufacturer’s support 
      delighted the <a href="https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2022/06/cardano-ledger-starts-letting-ada-investors-buy-send-and-receive-directly-on-ledger-live/">Cardano</a> community when it was first announced, with the integration’s rollout being applauded as well.</p><p>As CryptoGlobe reported, 
      Cardano hs been outperforming the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization Ethereum ($ETH) over the last few weeks and is already up 
      over 88% against it after making a recent low. Cardano’s performance is significant as it rivals Ethereum as a blockchain network that runs smart 
      contracts and decentralized applications (dApps).</p><p>Cardano’s network has been steadli growing, with  over 5 million native assets have now 
      having <a href="https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2022/06/cardano-ledger-starts-letting-ada-investors-buy-send-and-receive-directly-on-ledger-live/">been</a> minted on top of the Cardano blockchain, doubling the figure seen at the end of last year. Over 1,000 projects are building on top of 
      the network.</p><p>It’s worth noting Cardano’s price has been rising ahead of the Vasil hard fork, which according to Cardano’s founder Charles 
      Hoskinson is expected to bring a “massive performance improvement.” The crypto community has recently predicted that the price of Cardano’s native 
      $ADA token will surpass the $1 mark by the end of June, after the implementation of the fork.</p><p>The Vasil hard fork is a major upgrade that 
      will involve four <a href="https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2022/06/cardano-ledger-starts-letting-ada-investors-buy-send-and-receive-directly-on-ledger-live/">Cardano</a> Improvement Proposals (CIPs). The hard fork has already seen ADA outperform numerous other cryptocurrencies, even amid a 
      wider cryptocurrency market downturn exacerbated by the collapse of the Terra ecosystem. That performance saw ADA become the sixth-largest 
      cryptoasset by market capitalization this week, surpassing $XRP.</p><p>Featured image via Unsplash</p>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 21:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2022/06/cardano-ledger-starts-letting-ada-investors-buy-send-and-receive-directly-on-ledger-live/</link>
      <guid>https://www.cryptoglobe.com/latest/2022/06/cardano-ledger-starts-letting-ada-investors-buy-send-and-receive-directly-on-ledger-live/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
